Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records
1891-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art
COR0003.4.RG
175.5 Linear Feet
Although the Corcoran had no formal Special Events Office until 1979, the Gallery had a tradition of special events designed to cater to the CGA membership and to draw the Washington area public into the gallery. Prior 1979, special events which encompassed the Corcoran Lecture Group and the WAG were coordinated, at times, out of the Director's office, and at other times, were the responsibility of the Education Curator or the Public Relations office. As well as Gala Openings, members previews, and the annual Ball, the Corcoran offered membership concerts, the Sunday Afternoon Free Concerts, Thursday Evening Concerts and a variety of other musical concerts ranging from rather avant-garde experimental music and multi-media shows to the music of string quartets and madrigal singers. The records of the Special Events office trace the growth of the office's activities and responsibilities and witness the maturation of the Special Events office into an autonomous department of the CGA. These records date from 1891 to 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research.
When conducting research within The Corcoran Archives collections, please be advised of the following restrictions:
Records of the Board of Trustees (RG 1.0) and records of the Office of the Director (RG 2.0) are closed to research for 25 years from the date of creation.
Development records are closed to research (RG 3.2).
Access to student records is governed by the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which protects the privacy of student education records. Student records are closed for the lifetime of the student, and are presumed to be open 75 years after the date of record creation (RG 9.0 Series 4).
Personnel and financial records are closed for 50 years from date of record creation (RG 4.0).
Please see the Public Services and Instruction Librarian for assistance.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 17 series: Calendars, General events, Corporate and annual events, Musical events, Lectures, Washington Art Group, Administration, Invitations, Programs, Ephemera/publicity, Administration reords, Budget and financial records, Dailies, Events: openings and balls, Facilities use records, invitations, and Musical Evening Series (MES) records.
Please note that there are two processing projects for this record group. One undertaken in 1984 (Series 1-10) and the other in 2017 (Series 11-17). Several of the series titles are the same from the different projects. For ease of browsing, identical series titles have been sorted to appear adjacent to each other in the series list. This results in the series #s not always being in numerical order.
Historical narrative
This history was originally prepared by Corcoran Archivist Katherine M. Kovocs for publication in 1985 with the support of the National Endowment for the Humanities and was edited and updated in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
Although the Corcoran had no formal Special Events Office until 1979, the Gallery had a tradition of special events designed to cater to the CGA membership and to draw the Washington area public into the gallery. Prior to 1979, special events, encompassing the Corcoran Lecture Group and the WAG, were coordinated between the Director's office, the Public Relations office, and the Education Curator. The Corcoran put on Gala Openings, members previews, and the Annual Ball, and offered membership concerts, the Sunday Afternoon Free Concerts, Thursday Evening Concerts, and a variety of other musical concerts ranging from rather avant-garde experimental music and multimedia shows to the music of string quartets and madrigal singers.
In addition to musical programs, the Corcoran offered the public dance events, films, mime, video, and dramatic presentations. The Corcoran present a wide variety of interesting and informative events to its members and patrons, and the Gallery also acted as host for dinners for its corporate members. The use of the Corcoran facilities host for dinners promoted goodwill between local and national corporations and the CGA.
The Special Events Office coordinated these various events assuring the Gallery and its members of a smooth event. Depending on the nature of the event they could be responsible for invitations, flowers, caterers, security, sound systems, and performers.
The Special Events office continued its functions until the dissolution of the Gallery in 2014.
Names that are prominent in the Special Events records are: Sherry Ellman; Inga W. Wall Heck; Donalson F. Hoopes; Marilyn Montgomery; Melinda Moses; Elizabeth Punsalan; Judy Riley; Roger Selby; Roy Slade; Lorna Tilley; Gudmund Vigtel.
Custodial History
The records of the Special Events Office comprising Series 1-10 were transferred to the Corcoran Archives from the Special Events Office between January 1980 and 1984.
Scope and Contents
The records of the Special Events office trace the growth of the office's activities and responsibilities and witness the maturation of the Special Events office into an autonomous department of the CGA. The creation of the SED reflects a gradual increase in Gallery staff as well as an increased professionalization of administrative tasks and responsibilities, and therefore since 1979, the records are more cohesive and complete. Types of material in this records group includes brochures, calendars, planning files, correspondence, publicity material, memoranda, invitations, programs, announcements pre- and post-event reports, and menus -- and span the years circa 1891 to 2010.
Separated Materials
During processing in 1984 the following records were removed to another location:
Photographs moved to Archives audio-visual records Catalogs moved to Curatorial publications News clippings moved to Artist vertical files or History clipping files [handwritten note reads "many have been left in Events files] News Releases moved to Public Relations -- Press Release series
The following records were discarded: various unrelated correspondence; duplicates of correspondence (Xerox and carbon); duplicates of artists' publicity materials; purchase orders; film catalogs; and publicity on artists who did not perform.
Art; Artists; Museums; Washington (D.C.)
- Calendars [legacy series], 1964-1987; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Organized into 3 subseries: In-house calendars, Calendar of events copy, and Planning and appointment calendars.
  - In-house calendars, 1964-1987; Series 1 Subseries 1
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains typed and Xeroxed lists of events and their dates for staff use.
    - In-house Calendars, 1964-1987; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folders 1-10)
  - Calendar of events copy, 1970-1982; Series 1 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains rough drafts and final copy of the daily events for each month.
    - Calendar of Events Copy, 1970 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folders 11-19)
    - Calendar of Events Copy, 1971 January-June; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folders 20-24)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1982 June-August; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1981 January-February; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1980 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folders 27-28)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1979 October-December; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1973 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 30)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1971 January-May; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Monthly Calendar of Events, 1970 October-December; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 32)
  - Planning and appointment calendars, 1981-1984
    This subseries contains handwritten records of meetings, dates of performances, calendar deadlines, interviews with prospective performers, dinners.
    - Planning and Appointment Calendars, 1981 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - Planning and Appointment Calendars, 1982 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 106, Folders 34-45)
    - Planning and Appointment Calendars, 1983 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 106, Folders 46-57)
    - Planning and Appointment Calendars, 1984 January-December; Series 1 Subseries 3 (Box 106, Folders 58-69)
- General events [legacy series], 1960-1984; Series 2
  Organized into 7 subseries: Art events, Dance events, Dramatic events, Film, Dinners, Staff events, and Miscellaneous
  This series contains events that were not related to musical performances -- a category so large it warrants a series to itself.
  - Art events, Circa 1960-1985; Series 2 Subseries 1
    Arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries contains information on the dinners, previews and opening festivities of various art exhibitions. Includes correspondence, inter-office memos, menus, guest lists, lenders lists, programs and invitations.
    - Atget: Old France, 1982 January 27; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folders 70-71)
    - Banner Exhibition: OP and POP in Fabric, 1966 January 21; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 72)
    - Baziotes, 1966 March 26; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 73)
    - 28th Biennial Publicity/Sales, 1962; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folders 74-76)
    - 36th Biennial Opening, 1979 February; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 77)
    - Biennial: Western States Members Opening, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 78)
    - Black Folk Art: Artists/Lenders Dinner, 1982 January 13; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 79)
    - Black Folk Art: Members Opening, 1982 February 1982; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 80)
    - Black Folk Art: UIP-ARCO Reception, 1982 January 28; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 81)
    - Black Folk Art: Invitations/Press Conference, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 82)
    - Black Folk Art: AM Reception, 1982 January 13; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 83)
    - Black Folk Art, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 84)
    - Downing Exhibition: Sales, 1966-1967; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 85)
    - Roland Freeman Opening, 1983 January 23; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 86)
    - Sam Gilliam/SCM Corporation, 1983 March 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 87)
    - Sam Gilliam, 1983 March 22; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 88)
    - Sam Gilliam: Members Opening/SCM Corporation, 1983 March 23; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 89)
    - Mildred Hayward Show, 1966 June; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 90)
    - Paul Jenkins Exhibition, 1972-1973; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 91)
    - The Johnson Collection, 1965 January 12; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 92)
    - Phillip Morris VIP Reception, 1972 February 1; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folders 93-94)
    - Music, Music, Music, 1969; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 106, Folder 95)
    - Northern Light: King of Norway Reception, 1982 October 19; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Northern Light: Members Opening, 1982 September 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Northern Light: Press Conference, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Northern Light: Opening Reception, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folders 4-6)
    - Northern Light: Opening Reception Master Guest List, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Northern Light: Opening Reception Guest List, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Northern Light: Opening Reception, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Past and Present, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folders 10-17)
    - Photography Series, 1975; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - P.H. Polk Reception, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 19)
    - Charles Pratt Membership Opening, 1982 May 13; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 20)
    - George Rickey Exhibition, 1966; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Joane Thorne, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Tsai, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - Vantongerloo, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - Video Event, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 25)
    - Washington Artist Series, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folders 26-27)
    - Washington Artists Today, 1968; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 28)
    - Washington on the Potomac Members Opening, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 29)
    - Washington Print Club, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folder 30)
    - Yugoslav Show, 1966; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 107, Folders 31-33)
  - Dance events, Circa 1970-1985; Series 2 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains information on various dance performances, including ballet, jazz, interpretive dance. Includes programs, PR material, correspondence, interdepartmental memos, invitations and announcements.
    - Dance (General Info), Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 34)
    - Maria Alba: Spanish Dance, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 35)
    - Ava/Terri Dance Group, 1982 August 8; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 36)
    - The Dance Alliance, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 37)
    - Dance Circus, 1974 November 5; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 38)
    - Dance Vitae: Ritha Devi, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 39)
    - Dance Exhibition, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 40)
    - Feet First, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 41)
    - Free Association Dance Company, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 42)
    - Erick Hawkins Dance Company, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 43)
    - Mandala Folk Dance Ensemble, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 44)
    - Maryland Dance Company, 1977-1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 45)
    - Mimedance Theater, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 46)
    - Yasuko Nagamine, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 47)
    - Eleo Pomare Dance Company, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 48)
    - Soundstair Dance Company, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 49)
    - Murray Spalding Movement Art, Inc., Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 50)
    - Van Dyke, Jan and Dancers, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 51)
    - Carol Vaughn, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 52)
    - Washington Modern Dance Society, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 53)
    - Maida Withers and the Dance Construction Company, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 54)
  - Dramatic events, Circa 1960-1980; Series 2 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains information on various dramatic events, including poetry readings, Reader's theater, mime, dramatic interpretations/renderings. Includes PR material, programs, correspondence, memos, invitations and announcements.
    - Deborah Baber: Half the Battle, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 55)
    - Black Theater, 196[?] June 21; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 56)
    - Fraudulent Productions: Protoexodium, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 57)
    - Jonas Santos with the Bird and the Dirt, 1974 December 2; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 58)
    - Bob Stokes Reads Langston Hughes, 1969 September 23; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 107, Folder 59)
  - Film, Circa 1970-1980; Series 2 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains programs, PR materials, budgets, memos, invitations, announcements on film events.
    - 1974/1975, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 107, Folders 60-62)
    - 1976/1977, Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 107, Folders 63-64)
    - Children's International Film Festival, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 107, Folder 65)
  - Dinners, Circa 1980-1990; Series 2 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains correspondence, memos, menus pertaining to dinners held by various institutions and organizations in the Corcoran as well as dinners held in honor of Trustees, Board members, donors, benefactors, etc.
    - Donors Reception, 1982 December 1; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folders 66-67)
    - Frances B. Hammer Birthday Dinner, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 68)
    - Embassy of the Philippines Reception for President Marcos, 1982 September 17; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 69)
    - Charles Pratt Dinner, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 5 (Box 107, Folder 70)
  - Staff events, Circa 1980-1990; Series 2 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains memos, sign-up lists, menus, programs for the staff Christmas party, picnic, open houses, staff farewells, staff welcomes.
    - Archives Open House, 1980 January 22; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 71)
    - Coffee for Harriet Botwinick, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 72)
    - Welcome Michael Botwinick, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 73)
    - Carolyn Campbell's Farewell, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 74)
    - Staff Christmas Party, 1981 December 18; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 75)
    - Director's Dinner, 1983 March 7; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 76)
    - Slade Farewell Picnic, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 77)
    - Staff Luncheon, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 78)
    - Peter Thomas Departs, 1980 June 4; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 79)
    - Nygren Farewell Party, 1981 December 30; Series 2 Subseries 6 (Box 107, Folder 80)
  - Miscellaneous, Circa 1960-1980; Series 2 Subseries 7
    This subseries contains memos, guest lists, planning lists, committee lists, PR programs, accident reports for Balls, Masquerades, and Spring Dances.
    - Ball, 1968; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 81)
    - Ball, 1970; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 82)
    - Corcoran School of Art Benefit, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 83)
    - Ball, 1980; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 84)
    - Fashion Show, 1968; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 85)
    - Friends Introduction to Michael Botwinick, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 86)
    - Regional Scholastic Art Awards, Undated; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 87)
    - Women's Committee Music Festival, 1975 December 14; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 88)
    - Conference of Women in the Visual Arts, 1972 April 20-22; Series 2 Subseries 7 (Box 107, Folder 89)
- Events: openings and balls, Circa 1982 - 2004; Series 14
  Folders have been maintained in the order received when transferred to GW.
  This series contains records that detail the work of the Corcoran Gallery of Art special events division of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. These records date primarily from 1982 - 2004.
  - Loose Documents, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Major Donor Dinner, 1989 November 11; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Staff Holiday Party, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1989 Corcoran Open House, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lee Miller: Photographer Preview Reception, 1989 February 10; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1989 National Council Events, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marcel Bardone - Invitations, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Membser's Night at the Shop, 1989 November 16; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marchel Bardon RSVP, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lee Miller RSVPs, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Marcel Bardon Preview Reception, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Robert Adams - Membership Preveiw Reception, 1989 August 4; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 41st Biennial Press Preview, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 41st Biennial, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 41st Biennial Membership Preview, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 41st Biennial 1989 Invitation Lists, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minor Donor Concert Reception, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Corcoran Fanfare Guest/Invitation LIst, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - David Lloyd Kreeeger Show Membership Preview Reception, 1989 October 13; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - David Lloyd Kreeger Collection VIP Reception before Membership Opening, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Women's Committee David Lloyd Kreeger Reception, 1989 November 6; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Dudley Memorial Lecture, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Director's Evening, 1989 February 22; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Black Women Artists, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - I Dream a World RSVP, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - "I Dream a World" Press Preview, 1989 February 8; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "I Dream a World" Invitation List, 1989 February 8; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1989 People PHotos, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - US West/I Dream a World Reception, 1989; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - National Geographic Press Preview, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - National Geographic Preview, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Surrogate Selves Preview, 1989 January 25; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Spectrum Preview Reception, 1988 October 12; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Spectrum Series: Edelson, Puryear, Sanga, Stackhouse, 1988 October 12; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Spectrum - Charles Simonds, 1988 May 9; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Invitation List Spectrum: Charles Simonds, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Spectrum: Charles Simonds Press Preview, Circa 1987-1989; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Spectrum: January Exhibition Reception, Circa 1987-1989; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Spectrum Photographs, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - A Taste of Washington, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Three Russian Artists, 1988 May 4; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Three Soviet Artists Press Preview, 1988 May 4; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Invitation List Three Soviet Artists - Preview, 1988 May 4; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Invitation List Transco- Preview Reception, 1988 May 13; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Transco, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - American Masters Reception, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Hispanic Art in the U.S. Membership Preview Photos, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Hispanic Art, 1987-1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Hispanic Art in the U.S. Invitation List Preview Reception, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Hispanic Invitation, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hispanic Art in the U.S. Freinds Reception, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Hispanic Art ARCO, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Hispanic Press Preview, 1988; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hispanic Art in the U.S. Membership Reception, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hispanic Guest List, Circa 1987-1989; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Invitation List Hispanic, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hispanic Art Show, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Corcoran-Riggs-Sotheby's Benefit, 1987; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Welcome for Christina Orr Cahall, 1987 November 9; Series 14 (Box 10, Folder 30)